Edward U. Condon Papers 1920-1974 Mss.B.C752
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1920-1974; 128 boxes, 64 linear feet
  - Condon, E. U. (Box 19)
    - Studies on the Change in Permeability of Iron With Temperature, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Surface Attraction Forces, 3 folders (Box 25)
    - Swinging Catenary. (Box 25)
      See: Condon, E. U. Oscillations of a Suspended Chain
    - Taking A Chance in Physics (Address), 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Talk at Sunday Morning Services (Address) (Box 26)
    - Talk to District of Columbia Science Teachers (Address) (Box 26)
    - Taut String Method for Drawing Hyperbolas (Article) (Box 26)
    - Theoretical Basis of Analysis of X-Ray Florescence (Box 26)
    - Theories of Optical Rotatory Power (Article) (Box 26)
    - Theory of Intensity Distribution in Band Systems (Box 26)
    - Theory of Nuclear Structure (Address), 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Theory of Radiation from Paraboloid Reflectors (Report) (Box 26)
    - Time to Stop Baiting Scientists (Article) (Box 26)
    - Truth (Address) (Box 26)
    - Tunneling - How It All Started (Address), 3 folders (Box 26)
    - 25 Years After Hiroshima (Article) (Box 26)
    - UFOs I Have Loved and Lost (Address), 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Unexamined Life Is Not Worth Living (Address) (Box 26)
    - Universities and the Movement for Peace (Address), 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Urgent Necessity of Disarmament (Address) (Box 26)
    - Varieties of Scientific Communication (Address) (Box 26)
    - Vectors, Areors and Volumors (Address) (Box 26)
    - Wasting $1,250 a Second (Address) (Box 26)
    - Wave Guides, 4 folders (Box 26)
    - A Way of Looking at Physical Quantities and Their Dimensions. (Box 26)
      See: Log-Log Plot of Physical Quantities
    - We Have No Monopoly on Atomic Energy (Address) (Box 26)
    - Weakest Link (Address), 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Westinghouse Research in Nuclear Physics (Address) (Box 26)
    - What Is This New World? (Address), 4 folders (Box 26)
    - What Lies Ahead in Physics in the Next Fifty Years? (Address), 4 folders (Box 27)
    - What Next? (Address) (Box 27)
    - What the Physicists Are Trying To Do (Address) (Box 27)
    - What Westinghouse Contributed (Address) (Box 27)
    - What's Happened to Dave? (Article) (Box 27)
    - "Who's Next?", 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Will Project Plowshare Wreck Geneva Bomb Test Ban Negotiations?, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Work of the National Bureau of Standards (Address) (Box 27)
  - Flow of Liquid Helium Through Porous Vycor glass, Atkins, Kenneth Robert, 1920-1995; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Seki, H. (Box 27)
  - Quantum Mechanics and Radioactive Disintegration, 6 folders; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Gurney, Ronald W., (Ronald Wilfrid) (Box 27)
  - Quantum Mechanics, 4 folders; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Morse, Philip M., (Philip McCord), 1903-1985 (Box 27)
  - Atomic Structure (Book), Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Odabasi, Halis (Box 27-37)
    - Atomic Structure, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.1, 7 folders (Box 27)
    - Atomic Structure - 1: Notes, 7 folders (Box 27)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.2, 6 folders (Box 27)
    - Atomic Structure - 2: Notes, 23 folders (Box 27-28)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.3, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Atomic Structure - 3: Notes, 15 folders (Box 28)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.4, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Atomic Structure - 4: Notes, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - Atomic Structure - 4, 5: Notes, 7 folders (Box 29)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.5, 11 folders (Box 29)
    - Atomic Structure - 5: Notes, 13 folders (Box 29)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.6, 7 folders (Box 29)
    - Atomic Structure - 6: Notes, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Atomic Structure - 6, 7: Notes (Box 29)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.7, 16 folders (Box 30)
    - Atomic Structure - 7: Notes, 38 folders (Box 30-31)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.8, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Atomic Structure - 8: Notes, 46 folders (Box 31-32)
    - Atomic Structure - 8, 9: Notes, 7 folders (Box 32)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.9, 5 folders (Box 32)
    - Atomic Structure - Ch.10 (Box 32)
    - Atomic Structure - 10: Notes, 23 folders (Box 32-33)
    - Atomic Structure - 11: Notes, 3 folders (Box 33)
    - Atomic Structure - 12: Notes, 44 folders (Box 33-34)
    - Atomic Structure - 13: Notes, 10 folders (Box 34)
    - Atomic Structure - 14: Notes, 13 folders (Box 34-35)
    - Atomic Structure - 15: Notes (Box 35)
    - Atomic Structure - 17: Notes, 10 folders (Box 35)
    - Atomic Structure - 18: Notes, 6 folders (Box 35)
    - Atomic Structure - 19: Notes, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - Atomic Structure - 20: Notes, 15 folders (Box 35-36)
    - Atomic Structure - 21, 22: Notes, 6 folders (Box 36)
    - Atomic Structure - 22: Notes, 5 folders (Box 36)
    - Atomic Structure - Appendix 1, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Atomic Structure - Appendix 2, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Atomic Structure - Appendix 3, 5 folders (Box 36)
    - Atomic Structure - Misc. Graphs, 10 folders (Box 36)
    - Atomic Structure - Misc. Notes, 14 folders (Box 36-37)
  - Self-consistent Field Calculations of 1s 2 2s 2 2p3p Configuration in the Carbon Isoelectronic Sequence, Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Odabasi, Halis (Box 37)
  - Some examples of Parental Mixing in the N=7 and N=15 Isoelectronic Sequences, Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Odabasi, Halis (Box 37)
  - Handbook of Physics (Book), Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Odishaw, Hugh (Box 37)
    - Handbook of Physics, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Handbook of Physics. First Edition., 4 folders (Box 37)
    - Handbook of Physics. Second Edition., 6 folders (Box 37)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 1, 13 folders (Box 37)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 2, 6 folders (Box 37)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 2 (Box 38)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 3, 7 folders (Box 38)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 4, 17 folders (Box 38)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 5, 16 folders (Box 39)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 6, 27 folders (Box 39)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 6 (Box 40)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 7, 41 folders (Box 40)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 7 (Box 41)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 8, 43 folders (Box 41)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 8 (Box 42)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 9, 19 folders (Box 42)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 9 (Box 43)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 11, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 12, 5 folders (Box 43)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 13, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 14 (Box 43)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 15 (Box 43)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 16, 5 folders (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Book 23 (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Correspondence After Publication, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Index (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. McGraw-Hill, 10 folders (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Notes for Revision, 6 folders (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Part 2, Chapter 1, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Part 2, Chapter 2 (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Part 2, Chapter 8 (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Part 5, Chapter 12 (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Part 7, Chapter 1 (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Preliminary Notes, 3 folders (Box 44)
    - Handbook of Physics. Proofs, 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Theory of Atomic Spectra (Book), 7 folders; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Shortley, George, 1910 (Box 45)
  - Machine to Play Game of NIM, Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Derr, Willard A.; Tawney, Gerald L. (Box 45)
  - Picture Book of the Atoms (Book), 20 folders; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974; Zare, Richard N. (Box 45)
  - Condon, Emilie Honzik, 30 folders (Box 45-46)
  - Condon, Emilie Honzik. Letter From E. U. Condon 8 July 1949 (Box 46)
  - Condon, Emilie Honzik. Security Investigations, 6 folders (Box 46)
  - Condon, Herbert T. (Box 46)
  - Condon, Joseph Henry (Box 46)
  - Direct Evidence for Magnetic Domains in Silver, Condon, Joseph Henry and R. E. Walstedt (Box 46)
  - Condon, Paul Edward (Box 46)
  - Conference Book Service, Inc. (Box 46)
  - Conference on World Affairs, Boulder, Colo. (Box 46)
  - Conklin, Mrs. Nan H. (Box 46)
  - Conrad, Robert D. (Box 46)
  - Consumers Union of U.S., Inc., 4 folders (Box 46)
  - Cook, Allen B. (Box 46)
  - Cook, C. Sharp (Box 46)
  - Edmund Cook and Company (Box 46)
  - Cook, Fred J. The CIA (Box 46)
  - Cook, Fred J. Juggernaut: The Welfare State, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Cooper, John Sherman (Box 46)
  - Cooperative Foundation (Box 46)
  - Cooperative Institute for Research in Environmental Sciences, 3 folders (Box 46)
  - Corhart Refractories Company (Box 46)
  - Cornell College (Box 46)
  - Cornell University Press (Box 46)
  - Corning Glass Works (CGW) (Box 46-54)
    - Corning Glass Works, 36 folders (Box 46-47)
      - 1955, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - 1956, 3 folders (Box 46)
      - 1957 (Box 46)
      - 1958 (Box 46)
      - 1959, 3 folders (Box 46)
      - 1960, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - 1961, 3 folders (Box 46)
      - 1962, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - 1963, 3 folders (Box 47)
      - 1964 (Box 47)
      - 1966 (Box 47)
      - 1967, 4 folders (Box 47)
      - 1968, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Corning Glass Works, 8 folders (Box 47)
    - A New Look at the Fulcher Equation, Araujo, R. J. (Box 47)
    - Photochromic Glass, Araujo, R. J. (Box 47)
    - Analytical Procedure for Investigating the Room Temperature Dielectric Loss Factor Between 10 -2 and 10 6 Hz, Barney, W. H. (Box 47)
    - Review of Contract Program at the Polymer Research Corporation of America, Baum, George (Box 47)
    - Glass Crystallization, Beall, G. H. (Box 47)
    - Birefringence Constants of ... Glasses (Box 47)
    - Final Report. Magnetic Bubbles, Borrelli, N. F. (Box 47)
    - Formed Cermet Abrasives from the Glass System MgO-A12O3-B2O3-SiO2, Brothers, J. A. (Box 47)
    - Brothers, J. A. General Manufacturing Process: Formed Cermet Abrasive Grains (Box 47)
    - Brydges, W. T. Periodic Motions of a Falling Viscous Stream (Box 47)
    - Bubble Memories (Box 47)
    - Bubbles, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Camp, H. E. Gaslight Progress Report (Box 47)
    - Campbell, E. A. Gaslight Progress Report, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Characteristics of Stress Patterns for Strengthening, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Coal Gasification, 3 folders (Box 47)
    - Color Centers in Glass, 5 folders (Box 47)
    - Colored Glass, 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Comments on the Use of Outside Research Personnel at Owens, Illinois (Box 48)
    - Auto-Exhaust Catalyst, 5 folders; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 48)
    - On Diffusion Stress and Thermal Stress, 4 folders; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 48)
    - Supplementing Dr. Megla's Memo of November 6, 1970, on High Frequency Cables., Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 48)
    - Temperature Dependence on Glass Infra-Red Absorption at 9, Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 48)
    - Contract Research with the University of California, Berkeley, 7 folders (Box 48)
    - Contract Research with Washington University (Box 48)
    - Crystallization of alpha-Quartz Solid Solutions from Glass (Box 48)
    - Daniel's Reactor (Box 48)
    - BUN Analyzer: Evaluation of Immobilized Urease and Differential Conductivity, Dean, W. W. (Box 48)
    - Density of Glass (Box 48)
    - Devitrification of Tektite Glass (Box 48)
    - Dielectric Properties, 19 folders (Box 48-49)
    - Effects of Substrate Geometry on the Catalytic Efficiency of Automobile Exhaust Converters, 3 folders; Doman, R. C. (Box 49)
    - CORSTAR™ Sapphire Thermal Shock Testing Progress Report 1, Drake, R. W. (Box 49)
    - Very-Low-Expansion Glasses, Dumbaugh, W. H. (Box 49)
    - Eutectic Glasses of the Calcium Aluminosilicate System, Dumbaugh, W. H. (Box 49)
    - Durability of Noble Metals (Box 49)
    - Cell Geometry and Other Parameters Influencing Coating...on Warden Monoliths., Dwyer, T. J. (Box 49)
    - I. M. E. Application Studies on Glucose Isomerase Chemically Coupled to Zirconia Coated, 2 folders; Eaton, D. L. (Box 49)
    - E-C Vaporizing Process (Box 49)
    - Electrical Glass Working Seal (Box 49)
    - Electrical Properties, 4 folders (Box 49)
    - Electronics Research, 5 folders (Box 49)
    - Leaching Characteristics and Properties of Substrates Composed of Cordierite Plus Other Refractory Phases, Elmer, T. H. (Box 49)
    - Employment, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - European R & D Facility (Box 49)
    - Solid State Reactions in Glass-Ceramics, 2 folders; Evans, D. L. (Box 49)
    - Vitreous Silica Minus Oxygen Amorphous Silicon: A Model Study, Evans, D. L. (Box 49)
    - What Does Random Mean in Random Network?, Evans, D. L. (Box 49)
    - Use of Base Metal Oxide Catalyst for Automobile Exhaust Purification, Farrauto, R. J. (Box 49)
    - Bio-Organic Applications in Semiconductor Surface Physics., Fehlner, F. P. (Box 49)
    - Business Request for Bubble Memories, Fehlner, F. P. (Box 49)
    - Fining of ... Glass, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Fischer, David J. A Biomedical Business for Corning Glass Works... (Box 49)
    - Flannery, J. E. A Deductive Approach to Opal Glass "Flash Mark" (Box 49)
    - Flannery, J. E. Improving the Opacity of Phased-Separated Opal Glasses by Alterations of the Interfacial Tensions (Box 49)
    - Fotoform, 5 folders (Box 49)
    - Foundation - Science Fellows, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Frazier, J. F. Corning's Portable Electrical Appliances in Review (Box 49)
    - Fundamental Research (Box 49)
    - Fused Silica, 9 folders (Box 49-50)
    - Chemical Strengthening of Glass, Garfinkel, H. M. (Box 50)
    - An Atlas of Microstructure and Phase Identification of Selected Refractories Used in CGW Glass Manufacture, 3 folders; Geiger, G. A. (Box 50)
    - Glass Ceramics (Box 50)
    - Glass Melting, 4 folders (Box 50)
    - Gravely, B. T. Relations of Photometry (Box 50)
    - Hares, George B. Estimation of Glass Structure From Physical Properties ... (Box 50)
    - Heat Exchanger Design Calculations, 5 folders (Box 50)
    - Hertl, W. Micro-Sheet Glass/PVC Plastic Laminates (Box 50)
    - Hindley, N. K. Avalanche Ionization in Amorphous Semiconductors (Box 50)
    - History - A Century of Chemistry at CGW, 3 folders (Box 50)
    - Inside E-C Coated Tubing (Box 50)
    - Intensity-Dependent Light Absorption in Glass, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Interdiffusion of Alkali Metal Ions in Glass - Theoretical Discussion (Box 50)
    - Jenkins, W. H. Magnetic Memory Discs, Final Report, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Jones Filter Program, 12 folders (Box 50-51)
    - Final Report: Bubble Memories, Kendall, O. W. (Box 51)
    - Determination of Particle Size Distribution of Platinum in Emcom Devices, Korda, E. J. (Box 51)
    - Biomedical Devices and Instruments: Final Report, Kunz, H. J. (Box 51)
    - Low-Temperature Dielectric Bolometer, Lawless, W. N. (Box 51)
    - Solid-State Dielectric Refrigeration, 2 folders; Lawless, W. N. (Box 51)
    - Light Scattering in Glass, 15 folders (Box 51)
    - List of Technical Papers of CGW, 1954-61 (Box 51)
    - Feasibility of Using Gas- or Ion-Selective Electrodes as Detector in a Stat BUN Analyzer, Lubrand, G. J. (Box 51)
    - Machinable Glass-Ceramic (Box 51)
    - Glass Forming Processes, McLelland, G. W. (Box 51)
    - Management Conference, 3 folders (Box 51)
    - Venture Appraisal in the Maturing Corporation, Marchioni, A. J. (Box 51)
    - Optimization of Optical Waveguides: Electro-Optic Studies, Maurer, R. D. (Box 51)
    - Some Preliminary Estimates of Scattering Loss Effects in Glass Fibers., Maurer, R. D. (Box 51)
    - Abrasive Grain Development: X-Ray and Optical Studies in Boride Crystals Which Contribute to Improved Performance, Medrud, R. C. (Box 51)
    - A Computer-Controlled X-Ray Power Diffractometry System With On-Line Data Processing, Medrud, R. C. (Box 51)
    - Crystallographer's View of Crystallography in Industry, Medrud, R. C. (Box 51)
    - History of the Laminate Project: A Bibliography, Megles, J. E. (Box 51)
    - Laminated Technology of Glass and Glass-Ceramic Combinations, Megles, J. E. (Box 51)
    - Materials Compatibility in the Corstar™ Process, Meiling, G. S. (Box 51)
    - Metal Ions in a Spinel Type Structure (Box 51)
    - Melting, 5 folders (Box 51)
    - Miscellany, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Tests & Tools for Consumer Product Development, 3 folders; Morrissey, J. W. (Box 52)
    - Preparation of Damage-Free Wafers of Gadolinium Gallium Garnet, Murphy, J. A. (Box 52)
    - Oil Extraction Balls for the TOSCO II Process, Nelson, J. W. (Box 52)
    - Nuclear Magnetic and Electron Resonance in Glass, 6 folders (Box 52)
    - Operations Research (Box 52)
    - Operations Research. Notes on Production Scheduling (Box 52)
    - Organization Changes (Box 52)
    - Oriental Project (Box 52)
    - Proposal for a Tubular, Solar Thermal Collector, Ortabasi, U. (Box 52)
    - Magnetic Susceptibility of Iron-Group and Rare-Earth Ions in Glass, 2 folders; Ostertag, W. (Box 52)
    - Ion Implanted Diffusion Sources, 2 folders; Perloff, D. S. (Box 52)
    - Ion-Implanted Resistors. Part 1., Perloff, D. S. (Box 52)
    - Photochromic Silicate Glasses. (Box 52)
    - Photon to Electron Image Converter and Intensifier (Box 52)
    - Photosensitive Glass, 4 folders (Box 52)
    - Photosensitive Glass Decorating (Box 52)
    - AIM System Pilot Plant Scale-Up, Pitcher, W. H., Jr. (Box 52)
    - Pressure Bleaching of Glass (Box 52)
    - Production Scheduling (Box 52)
    - Barium Titanate Ceramic Dielectric Materials: Chemical Analysis by X-Ray Emission, Quinn, A. P. (Box 52)
    - Radiation Effects on Glass, 7 folders (Box 52)
    - Radiative Heat Transfer in Hot Glass, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Mixed Halide Effects, Randall, E. N. (Box 52)
    - Mixed-Ion Effects in Halide Glasses, Randall, E. N. (Box 52)
    - Rapid Selective Complexometric Determination of Zirconium (Box 52)
    - Optimum Strengthening of Glass by Ion Exchange, 3 folders; Rauscher, H. E. (Box 52)
    - Research Fellowship Program (Box 52)
    - Research Management Corp. An Analysis of the Potential Government Market for CGW, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Research Progress Meetings (Box 52)
    - Resignation of Directorship, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Rheology, 5 folders (Box 53)
    - Effect of Adsorbed Carbon Dioxide on the Conductance of Amorphous Chalcogenide Films, Rockstad, H. K. (Box 53)
    - Review of Theory and Applications of NMR, EPR, and Magnetic Susceptibility, Schreurs, J. W. H. (Box 53)
    - A Literature Survey and Bibliography of Microanalytical Chemistry, Schucker, G. D. (Box 53)
    - Effects of Very Minor Oxide Additions to the Annealing Temperature of Vitreous Silica, Schultz, P. C. (Box 53)
    - Scintillation in Glass, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Semi-Conducting "EC" Films, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Refractive Index Photochromic Glasses, Seward, T. P., III. (Box 53)
    - Theory of Polarizing Glass, Seward, T. P., III. (Box 53)
    - Sheet Glass, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - New and Renewed Efforts in Application of SEACOR Technology, Shoup, R. D. (Box 53)
    - What's New in Glass?, Smith, G. P. (Box 53)
    - Electro-optic Properties of Hot-Pressed Relaxation Dielectrics, Smith, J. W. (Box 53)
    - Electron Spectroscopy for Chemical Analysis, Stephenson, D. A. (Box 53)
    - Instructions on the Use of Corset, Stephenson, D. A. (Box 53)
    - Some Interesting Examples of Photochemical and Thermal Reactions in Glass Strength, 10 folders; Stookey, S. D. (Box 53)
    - Strength of Glass (Box 53)
    - Stress Inside of Cylindrical Steam Gauge Glass (Box 53)
    - Preliminary Report: Properties of Neptune Glasses, Tarzca, W. H. (Box 53)
    - Technical Requests (Box 53)
    - Technical Staffs Division, 5 folders (Box 53)
    - Technical Staffs Division. Reports, 2 folders (Box 53)
    - Temperature Dependence of Glass Infra-Red Absorption at 9? (Box 53)
    - Thermal Stress Due to Heating or Cooling a Flat Slab of Glass. (Box 53)
    - Surface Photovoltage Spectroscopy - A New Tool for Studying Catalysis, Tick, P. A. (Box 53)
    - Trace Metals in New York State Fish, Tong, S. S. C. (Box 53)
    - Transformation Range, 6 folders (Box 53)
    - Trip Report - Ford Motor Co. (Box 54)
    - Ultrahigh Pressure in Glass (Box 54)
    - Viscous Flow in Cane and Tube Drawing, 7 folders (Box 54)
    - Vycor Brand Glass (Box 54)
    - Durability of WARDEN Process ZP-167 Corderite Monoliths, Walters, H. V. (Box 54)
    - Granular Refractory Superconductors, Watson, J. H. P. (Box 54)
    - Gaseous Diffusion to a Catalytic Surface, 3 folders; Weber, William A. (Box 54)
    - Affinity Chromotography, Weetall, H. H. (Box 54)
    - Continuous Production of Dextrose From Cornstarch, Weetall, H. H. (Box 54)
    - Course Notes, Immobilized Enzymes, Weetall, H. H. (Box 54)
    - Enzymes - Industrialized, Weetall, H. H. (Box 54)
    - Immobilized Enzymes and Their Application in the Food and Beverage Industry, Weetall, H. H. (Box 54)
    - Color Control Specifications for Bausch and Lomb Opthalmic Glasses, Werner, A. J. (Box 54)
    - Color Control Specification for Glass Code 8314, Werner, A. J. (Box 54)
    - Color Control Specification for Glass Code 8315, Werner, A. J. (Box 54)
    - Heteropoly Tungstodicuprates..., Wexell, D. R. (Box 54)
    - Silk Screen Application of Thick Film Noble Metal Heating Elements, Williams, T. (Box 54)
    - X-Ray Fluorescence Analysis, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Immobilized Enzymes and Antibodies, Yaverbaum, S. (Box 54)
    - Dynamo Project: Final Report, Yost, T. J. (Box 54)
  - Cornog, R. (Box 54)
  - Coryell, Charles D. (Box 54)
  - Cosmos Club, 8 folders (Box 54)
  - Coulson, C. A. (Box 54)
  - Council on Christian Social Progress (Box 54)
  - Council on Consumer Information (Box 54)
  - Courant, Richard, 4 folders (Box 54)
  - Course Materials (Box 54-59)
    - Applied Mathematics Lectures, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Electromagnetic Theory of Light, 11 folders (Box 54-55)
    - Examination Papers - Undergraduate (Box 55)
    - Physics 32, 5 folders (Box 55)
    - Physics A101, 7 folders (Box 55)
    - Physics 105, 12 folders (Box 55)
    - Physics 105 - Mechanics, 15 folders (Box 55)
    - Physics 105 (and 106) (Box 55)
    - Physics 106, 11 folders (Box 55-56)
    - Physics s112 - Electricity and Magnetism, 9 folders (Box 56)
    - Physics 117 - 118, 13 folders (Box 56)
    - Physics 121 - 122, 6 folders (Box 56)
    - Physics 199 #1 (note: no folder #2) (Box 56)
    - Physics 201 #2 (note: no folder #1) (Box 56)
    - Physics 201f, 10 folders (Box 56-57)
    - Physics 201 - 202, 16 folders (Box 57)
    - Physics 462 - Mechanics of Continuous Media, 6 folders (Box 57)
    - Physics 503 - Atomic Physics, 9 folders (Box 57)
    - Physics 503-504 - Atomic Physics, 6 folders (Box 57)
    - Physics 560-561, 12 folders (Box 58)
    - Quantum Mechanics, 18 folders (Box 58)
    - Quantum Mechanics - Lecture Notes, 11 folders (Box 58)
    - Selected Topics in Theoretical Physics, 9 folders (Box 58-59)
    - Statistical Mechanics, 11 folders (Box 59)
  - Covington, Burling, Rublee, Acheson and Shorb (Box 59)
  - Cox, John P. (Box 59)
  - Cox, R. T. (Box 59)
  - Crafts, Edward C. (Box 59)
  - Craig, Roy (Box 59)
  - Cranberg, Lawrence (Box 59)
  - Crane, E. M., Jr. (Box 59)
  - Crane, E. V. (Box 59)
  - Crane, H. R. (Box 59)
  - Creutz, E. C. (Box 59)
  - Crime, 7 folders (Box 59)
  - Crime. State Responses to Circular Letter (Box 59)
  - Crofts, Alfred (Box 59)
  - Reduced Matrix Elements of Two-Electron Double-Vector Operators for F 4 and F 5, Crosswhite, Hannah. (Box 59)
  - Crotty, Homer D. (Box 59)
  - Crow, Wayman (Box 59)
  - Crowe, Lawson (Box 59)
  - Crowe, M. O'L. (Box 59)
  - Crowell-Collier Publishing Co. (Box 59)
  - Crusade by Truth and Fact for World Peace (Box 59)
  - Cuba, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Cunningham, Richard E. (Box 59)
  - Cunningham, S. B. (Box 59)